Farbstein, Leonard; Papers apap245
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- The 91st Congress, 1963-1970; Undated; 7; 11.2 cubic ft.
  - H. R. 5554: A Bill to Provide A Special Milk Program for Children, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - H. R. 5567: A Bill to Permit the Mailing by Nonprofit Organizations Under the Third-Class Bulk Mail Provisions of Title 39 of the United States Code, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - H. R. 5583: A Bill for Amendment of Title 18 of the United States Code, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - H. R. 5978: A Bill for Amendment of Title 4 of the Social Security Act, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - H. R. 6037: A Bill to Establish a Department of Consumer Affairs (Also Contains H. R. 17097), 1969 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - H. R. 6041: A Bill for Amendment to the Intergovernmental Cooperation Act of 1968, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - H. R. 6071: A Bill to Enable Consumers to Protect Themselves Against Arbitrary, Erroneous, and Malicious Credit Information, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - H. R. 6279: A Bill for Amendment of Title 2 of the Social Security Act, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - H. R. 6469: A Bill for Amendment of Certain Provisions of Existing Low- and Moderate-Income Housing, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - H. R. 6492: A Bill for Amendment of Title 2 of the Social Security Act, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - H. R. 6502: A Bill to Promote the Peaceful Resolution of International Conflict, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - H. R. 6635: A Bill for Amendment of the Public Assistance Provisions of the Social Security Act, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - H. R. 6637: A Bill to Establish a Federal Sabbatical Program to Improve the Quality of Teaching in the Nation's Elementary or Secondary Schools, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - H. R. 7332: A Bill for Amendment of the Federal Property and Administrative Services Act of 1949, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - H. R. 7467: A Bill to Extend from Two Years to Five Years the Period of Salary Protection and Pay Saving for Postal Field Service and Classified Employees Who Are Reduced in Salary or Grade, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - H. R. 7581: A Bill for Amendment of Title 10 of the United State Code (Also Contains H. R. 18880), 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - H. R. 7585: A Bill for Amendment of the Internal Revenue Code of 1954, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - H. R. 7734: A Bill for Amendment of the Federal Water Pollution Control Act, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - H. R. 7760: A Bill to Provide Supplemental Appropriations to Fully Fund Programs to Build Three Hundred Units of Low- and Moderate- Income Housing for the Fiscal Year 1969 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - H. R. 7977: A Bill for Amendment of Section 231(b) of the Trade Expansion Act of 1962, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - H. R. 8042: A Bill to Establish a National Economic Conversion Commission (Also Contains Related Bills), 1963-1965; 1969 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - H. R. 8280: A Bill for Amendment of Title 2 of the Social Security Act, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - H. R. 8281: A Bill for Amendment of Title 18 of the Social Security Act (Also Contains Related Bills), 1966-1967; 1969 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - H. R. 8282: A Bill for Amendment of Title 2 of the Social Security Act (Also Contains H. R. 15388), 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - H. R. 8283: A Bill for Amendment of Titles 4 and 19 of the Social Security Act, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - H. R. 8622: A Bill to Create a Department of Youth Affairs, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - H. R. 8767: A Bill to Exempt from the Antitrust Laws Certain Joint Newspaper Operating Arrangement, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - H. R. 8772: A Bill to Permit a State to Elect to Use Funds from the Highway Trust Fund for Purpose of Preventing and Controlling Air Pollution, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - H. R. 8937: A Bill to Permit Officers and Employees of the Federal Government to Elect Coverage Under the Old Age, Survivors, and Disability Insurance System, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - H. R. 9040: A Bill for Amendment of the Federal Hazardous Substances Act, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - H. R. 9229: A Bill to Provide for Improved Employee-Management Relations in the Postal Service (Also Contains Related Bills), 1969 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - H. R. 9230: A Bill for Amendment of Title 2 of the Social Security Act (Also Contains H. R. 3782), 1969 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - H. R. 9280: A Bill to Provide Relocation Housing for Persons Displaced by Federally Conducted or Federally Aided Acquisition of Real Property (Also Contains Related Bills), 1966-1967; 1969 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - H. R. 9281: A Bill for Amendment of the Railroad Retirement Act of 1937, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - H. R. 9282: A Bill to Provide for Public Participation in the Development of Federally Aided Highways, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - H. R. 9382: A Bill to Establish a Pollution Disaster Fund, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - H. R. 9575: A Bill for Amendment of the Foreign Assistance Act of 1961, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - H. R. 9643: A Bill for Amendment of the Economic Opportunity Act of 1964, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - H. R. 9678: A Bill for Amendment of the Internal Revenue Code of 1954 (Also Contains S. 422), 1969 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - H. R. 9832: A Bill for Amendment of the Public Works and Economic Development Act of 1965 (Also Contains Related Bills), 1967-1969 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - H. R. 9896: A Bill for Amendment of Internal Revenue Code of 1954, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - H. R. 9954: A Bill for Amendment of National Labor Relations Act, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - H. R. 10014: A Bill for Amendment of Act Entitled "An Act to Promote the Safety of Employees and Travelers Upon Railroads by Limiting the Hours of Service of Employees Thereon" (Also Contains H. R. 10720), 1965-1967; 1969 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - H. R. 10239: A Bill for Amendment of Sugar Act of 1948, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - H. R. 10291: A Bill for Amendment of Title 18 of the Social Security Act, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - H. R. 10384: A Bill for Amendment of Immigration and Nationality Act (Also Contains H. R. 18369), 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - H. R. 10385: A Bill to Provide for the Redistribution of Unused by Quota Numbers, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - H. R. 10386: A Bill for Amendment of Immigration and Nationality Act, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - H. R. 10494: A Bill for Amendment of Title 18 of United States Code, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - H. R. 10495: A Bill for Amendment of Title 18 of the Social Security Act (Also Contains H. R. 9859), 1967; 1969 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - H. R. 10554: A Bill to Establish an Urban Mass Transportation Trust Fund, 1969-1969 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - H. R. 10589: A Bill for Amendment of Uniform Code of Military Justice (1 of 2), 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - H. R. 10589: A Bill for Amendment of Uniform Code of Military Justice (2 of 2), 1966; 1968-1970 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - H. R. 10728: A Bill for Amendment of the Food Stamp Act of 1964, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - H. R. 10861: A Bill for Amendment of the Internal Revenue Code of 1954, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - H. R. 11102: A Bill for Amendment of the Provisions of the Public Health Services Act (Also Contains H. R. 7059), 1969 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - H. R. 11244: A Bill to Establish a World Economic Cooperation and National Development Organization, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - H. R. 11347: A Bill for Amendment of Title 2 of the Social Security Act, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - H. R. 11360: A Bill for Amendment of the Internal Revenue Code of 1954, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - H. R. 11621: A Bill to Assure an Opportunity for Employment to Every American Seeking Work and to Make Available the Education and Training Needed by Any Persons to Qualify for Employment Consistent with His Highest Potential and Capabilities, 1967; 1969 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - H. R. 11662: A Bill for Amendment of Titles 1, 10, 14, 16, and 19 of the Social Security Act, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - H. R. 11762: A Bill for Amendment of the Legislative Reorganization Act of 1946, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - H. R. 11808: A Bill for Amendment of the Small Business Act to Make Crime Protection Insurance Available to Small Business Concerns, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - H. R. 11817: A Bill to Prescribe Standards for Congressional Redistricting, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - H. R. 11907: A Bill to Impose an Excess Profits Tax on the Income of Corporations During the Present Emergency, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - H. R. 11935: A Bill to Extend to Every Person Classified or Processed Under the Selective Service Act, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - H. R. 12042: A Bill for Amendment of Section 1102 of the Federal Aviation Act of 1958, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - H. R. 12046: A Bill for Amendment of Title 1 of the International Claims Settlement Act of 1949 (Also Contains S. 1935), 1965; 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - H. R. 12116: A Bill for Amendment of the Public Health Service Act, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - H. R. 12220: A Bill to Repeal the Emergency Detention Act of 1950, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - H. R. 12264: A Bill for Amendment of the Fish and Wildlife Coordination Act, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - H. R. 12265: A Bill to Establish a Joint Committee on Environmental Quality, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - H. R. 12459: A Bill for Amendment of the Communications Act of 1934, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - H. R. 12462: A Bill to Authorize the Administrator of General Services to Transfer Certain Airspace for Use for Housing Purposes, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - H. R. 12575: A Bill for Amendment of Title 2 of the Social Security Act, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - H. R. 12641: A Bill to Incorporate Pop Warner Little Scholars, Incorporated, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - H. R. 12774: A Bill to Provide A More Effective Approach to the Problem of Developing and Maintaining a Rational Relationship Between Building Code Requirements and Building Technology in the United States, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - H. R. 12796: A Bill for Amendment of Title 18 of the United States Code, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - H. R. 12797: A Bill for Amendment of Title 18 of the Social Security Act, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - H. R. 12894: A Bill to Provide for the Comprehensive Control of Narcotic Addiction and Drug Abuse, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - H. R. 12898: A Bill to Authorize the Administrator of General Services to Transfer Certain Airspace for Use of Housing Purposes, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - H. R. 12946: A Bill for Amendment of the Housing and Urban Development Act of 1968, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - H. R. 13013: A Bill for Amendment of the Internal Revenue Code of 1954, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - H. R. 13138: A Bill for Amendment of Public Law 87-849, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - H. R. 13225: A Bill for Amendment of the Clear Air Act (1 of 2), 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - H. R. 13225: A Bill for Amendment of the Clean Air Act (2 of 2), 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - H. R. 13281: A Bill to Require Advertising for Gasoline that Contains Lead to Contain a Statement that the Gasoline Contains Lead and that Inhaling Its Fumes Can be Fatal, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - H. R. 13317: A Bill to Provide Federal Financial Assistance to Help Cities and Communities of the United States Develop and Carry Out Intensive Local Programs to Eliminate the Causes of Lead-Based Paint Poisoning, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - H. R. 13318: A Bill to Provide that Federal Assistance to a State or Local Government or Agency for Renovation of Housing Shall be Made Available Only on Condition that the Recipient Carry Out an Effective Plan for Eliminating Lead-Based Paint Poisoning, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - H. R. 13319: A Bill for Amendment of the Federal Food, Drug, and Cosmetic Act to Provide for the Establishment of a National Drug Testing and Evaluation Center (Also Contains S. 2729), 1969 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - H. R. 13320: A Bill to Provide Federal Financial Assistance to Help Cities and Communities of the United States Develop and Carry Out Intensive Local Programs to Detect and Treat Incidents of Lead-Based Paint Poisoning, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - H. R. 13321: A Bill for Amendment of Internal Revenue Code of 1954, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - H. R. 13339: A Bill to Recognize that Executive Branch of the Government by Transferring to the Secretary of the Interior Certain Functions of the Secretary of Agriculture, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - H. R. 13423: A Bill for Amendment of Food Stamp Act of 1964, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - H. R. 13479: A Bill to Provide Appropriations for Sharing of Federal Revenues with Cities, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - H. R. 13530: A Bill to Provide for Quarterly Reporting to the Congress by the Secretary of Defense, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - H. R. 13625: A Bill to Establish a National Program to Provide Income Supplements to Every Family in Need Thereof (Identical to H. R. 13476), 1969 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - H. R. 13650: A Bill for Amendment of Title 38 of the United States Code, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - H. R. 13686: A Bill for Amendment of Internal Revenue Code of 1954, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - H. R. 13870: A Bill for Amendment of Title 12 of the National Housing Act, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - H. R. 13905: A Bill for Amendment of Title 38 of the United States Code, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - H. R. 13981: A Bill to Authorize the Interstate Commerce Commission (Also Contains S. 1980), 1969 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - H. R. 14011: A Bill to Provide for the Establishment of a Commission on Marihuana, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - H. R. 14064: A Bill to Establish a Grant-in-Aid Program to Encourage the Licensing by the States of Motor Vehicle Mechanics, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - H. R. 14148: A Bill for Amendment of Social Security Act (Also Contains H. R. 13840), 1969 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - H. R. 14223: A Bill to Control the Use of Hypnosis in Criminal Proceedings, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - H. R. 14329: A Bill to Prohibit Hiring Professional Strikebreakers in Interstate Labor Disputes, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - H. R. 14330: A Bill to Improve Judicial Machinery by Providing Federal Jurisdiction for Certain Types of Class Actions, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - H. R. 14331: A Bill for Amendment of Title 39 of United States Code, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - H. R. 14402: A Bill for Amendment of Sugar Act of 1948, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - H. R. 14430: A Bill for Amendment of Social Security Act, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - H. R. 14479: A Bill to Authorize the Appropriation of Increased Annual Amounts for the Conduct of Research by the Division of Narcotic Addiction and Drug Abuse in the National Institute of Health, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - H. R. 14500: A Bill to Provide for the Continuation of Programs Authorized Under the Economic Opportunity Act of 1964, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - H. R. 14535: A Bill to Simulate the Development, Production, and Distribution in Interstate Commerce of Low-Emission Motor Vehicles, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - H. R. 14627: A Bill for Amendment of the Federal Trade Commission Act, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - H. R. 14640: A Bill to Prohibit the Procurement of California Table Grapes by the Department of Defense, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - H. R. 14741: A Bill for the Amendment of Title 23 of the United States Code to Revise the Next Due Date for the Cost Estimate for the Interstate System, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - H. R. 14759: A Bill to Permit the Governor of a State to Elect to Use Funds from the State's Federal Aid Highway System Apportionment, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - H. R. 14816: A Bill for Amendment of Fair Packaging and Labeling Act, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - H. R. 14867: A Bill for Amendment of Clean Air Act, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - H. R. 14910: A Bill to Provide a Program to Improve the Opportunity of Students in Elementary and Secondary Schools to Study Cultural Heritages of the Major Ethnic Groups in the Nation, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - H. R. 15025: A Bill to Provide a Program of Pollution Control in Selected River Basins and Waterways of the United States through Comprehensive Planning and Financial Assistance, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - H. R. 15092: A Bill to Revise the Immigration and Nationality Bill, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - H. R. 15167: A Bill for Amendment of Title 28 of the United States Code, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - H. R. 15168: A Bill for Amendment of Title 2 of the Social Security Act, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - H. R. 15224: A Bill for Amendment of Title 10 of the United States Code, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - H. R. 15262: A Bill for Amendment of the National Traffic and Motor Vehicle Safety Act of 1966 (1 of 2), 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - H. R. 15262: A Bill for Amendment of the National Traffic and Motor Vehicle Safety Act of 1966 (2 of 2), 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - H. R. 15289: A Bill to Authorize the United States Commissioner of Education to Establish Educational Programs, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - H. R. 15293: A Bill for Amendment of Title 18 of the Social Security Act, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - H. R. 15301: A Bill to Encourage State and Local Governments to Reform Their Tax Systems, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - H. R. 15302: A Bill to Encourage State and Local Governments to Reform Their Tax Systems, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - H. R. 15303: A Bill to Encourage State and Local Governments to Adopt More Equitable Personal Income Taxes, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - H. R. 15319: A Bill to Establish a Commission to Study and Investigate Incidents of Alleged Mistreatment Against Citizens of South Vietnam, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - H. R. 15487: A Bill to Increase the Actuarial Soundness of the Government National Mortgage Association, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - H. R. 15702: A Bill for Amendment of the Omnibus Crime Control and Safe Streets Act of 1968, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - H. R. 15828: A Bill for Amendment of the National Environmental Policy Act of 1969, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - H. R. 16006: A Bill for Amendment of the Railroad Retirement Act of 1937, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - H. R. 16007: A Bill for Amendment of Title 2 of the Social Security Act, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - H. R. 16224: A Bill for the Amendment of Title 18 of the Social Security Act, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - H. R. 16328: A Bill for Newsmen's Privilege Act of 1970 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - H. R. 16470: A Bill for Amendment of the Omnibus Crime Control and Safe Streets Act of 1968, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - H. R. 16520: A Bill to Provide for a Comprehensive Program for the Control of Noise, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - H. R. 16551: A Bill for Amendment of the Clayton Antitrust Act, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - H. R. 16574: A Bill to Preserve and Protect the Confidentiality of First-Class Mail, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - H. R. 16395: A Bill for Amendment to the Food Stamp Act of 1964, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - H. R. 16686: A Bill to Provide for the Issuance of a Gold Medal to the Widow of the Reverend Doctor Martin Luther King Jr., 1970 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - H. R. 16713: A Bill for Amendment of Section 208 of the National Emissions Standards Act, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - H. R. 16876: A Bill for Amendment to Section 152(a)(7) of the Internal Revenue Code of 1954, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - H. R. 16681: A Bill to Establish a Senior Citizens Skill and Talent Utilization Program, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - H. R. 16947: A Bill to Provide for the Development of a Uniform System of Quality Grades for Consumer Food Products, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - H. R. 16951: A Bill to Require that Durable Consumer Products be Labeled as to Durability and Performance, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - H. R. 16953: A Bill to Require that Certain Durable Products be Prominently Labeled as to Date of Manufacture, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - H. R. 16955: A Bill to Require that Certain Drugs and Pharmaceuticals be Prominently Labeled as to the Date Beyond Which Potency Becomes Diminished, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - H. R. 16957: A Bill to Require that Certain Short Shelf-Life Durable Products be Prominently Labeled as to the Date Beyond Which Performance Life Becomes Diminished, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - H. R. 16990: A Bill to Prohibit the Importation, Manufacture, Sale, Purchase, Transfer, Receipt, or Transportation of Hand Guns Affecting Interstate or Foreign Commerce, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - H. R. 17005: A Bill to Require the Dating of Packaged Foods, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - H. R. 17005: A Bill for Amendment to the Fair Packaging and Labeling Act, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - H. R. 17006: A Bill for Amendment of the Fair Packaging and Labeling Act, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - H. R. 17025: A Bill for Amendment of the Fair Packaging and Labeling Act, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - H. R. 17083: A Bill for Amendment of the Fair Packaging and Labeling Act, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - H. R. 17199: A Bill for Amendment of the National Emission Standards Act, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - H. R. 17200: A Bill for Amendment of the National Emission Standards Act, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - H. R. 17201: A Bill to Impose an Excise Tax on Automobiles Based on Their Horsepower and Emission of Pollutants, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - H. R. 17202: A Bill to Impose an Excise Tax on Automobiles Based on Their Horsepower and Emission of Pollutants, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - H. R. 17203: A Bill to Permit the Governor of a State to Elect to Use Funds from the State's Federal-Aid Highway System Apportionment, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - H. R. 17205: A Bill to Establish a National Bank for Cooperative Housing (1 of 2), 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - H. R. 17205: A Bill to Establish a National Bank for Cooperative Housing (2 of 2), 1966; 1968-1970 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - H. R. 17206: A Bill for Amendment of the Fair Packaging and Labeling Act, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - H. R. 17207: A Bill for Amendment of the Public Assistance Provisions of the Social Security Act, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - H. R. 17208: A Bill for Amendment of Title 38 of the United States Code, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - H. R. 17209: A Bill to Assist in Combating Crime by Reducing the Incidents of Recidivism, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - H. R. 17239: A Bill to Provide that Air Quality Levels Shall be Taken Into Account in the Planning of Federal-Aid Highway Projects, 1968-1970 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - H. R. 17247: A Bill to Provide that the Federal Office Building at 26 Federal Plaza New York, New York Shall be Named the "Robert Francis Kennedy Federal Office Building", 1970 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - H. R. 17263: A Bill for Amendment of Title 23 of the United States Code, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - H. R. 17277: A Bill to Make Available to Certain Organized Tribes of Indians Residing on Indian Reservations Certain Benefits, Care, or Assistance, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - H. R. 17280: A Bill to Permit the Governor of a State to Elect to Use Funds from the State's Federal-Aid Highway System Apportionment, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - H. R. 17281: A Bill to Permit the Governor of a State to Elect to Use Funds from the State's Federal-Aid Highway System Apportionment, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - H. R. 17341: A Bill to Provide for Orderly Trade in Textile Articles and Articles of Leather Footwear, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - H. R. 17437: A Bill for Amendment of the National Emission Standards Act, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - H. R. 17438: A Bill to Impose an Excise Tax on Automobiles Based on Their Horsepower and Emission of Pollutants, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - H. R. 17439: A Bill to Permit the Governor of a State to Elect to Use Funds from the State's Federal-Aid Highway System Apportionment, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - H. R. 17442: A Bill for Amendment of the Omnibus Crime Control and Safe Streets Act of 1968, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - H. R. 17698: A Bill for Amendment of Title 32 of the United States Code, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 17)